TWUA Local 406 Records 6332
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
TWUA Local 406 Records
1948-1975
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Textile Workers' Union of America (TWUA)
6332
1 cubic feet
1 linear ft.
Records.
7544861
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, April 20, 2015
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, March 07, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Textile workers--Labor unions--New York (State); Clothing workers--Labor unions--New York (State); Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union --Archives; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union --Archives; Textile Workers Union of America. Local 406--Archives; Textile Workers Union of America.; Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees --Archives; UNITE HERE (Organization) --Archives
7544861
- Local 406 - Grievance No. 3051 "Job Posting", 1974 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Grievance #3122 - Denis Lacroix, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Maremont Grievance 3151 - George Kent, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Local 406 - Grievance No. 2728 Chrome Platers/chrome plater helpers, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Grievance No. 3196 - D. Ledoux, Overtime on Saturday, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Grievance No. 3081 - Reposting of Job Opening for Repair Machinist, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Grievance No. 3081 Transcript pg. 1-136, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Local 406 - Grievance No. 3134, Job Posting Plant-wide, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Grievance No. 3134 - Company's Post-Hearing Brief, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Grievance No. 3134 - Transcript pg. 1-111, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Grievance No. 3040 - Leadman Promotion, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Arbitration Article (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Group Grievance No. 3108, 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Grievance No. 2708 - Edward Walton, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Grievance No. 3155 - Air Tester, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Grievance No. 3114 - Wm McAuley, 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Contract Misinterpretation by Maremont (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Grievance No. 3040 - Transcript pg. 1-164, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Grievance No. 3062 - Gerald Stewart, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Grievance No. 3060, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Grievance Nos. 2957, 2961, 2962, 2963, and 2965, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Grievance 3165 - L. Leclair, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Group Grievance No. 3162, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Grievance No. 2856 - Defective Parts, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Agreements, 1948-1949 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Agreements, 1960-1969 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Agreements, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Group Insurance (Box 1, Folder 28)